VAUGHN: Ah, come in, gentlemen.
啊, 进来, 先生们
- Well, Gregory, success?
- I don't know yet, sir.
- 怎样, Gregory, 成功了？ - 我还不知道, 先生
We've added narrow bandwidth transducers.
Should make transmission more directional.
我们给加了窄幅变换器, 应该会让发送时更有方向性
Good, good. Show me.
好, 很好, 展示一下
This is madness.
这太疯狂了
- That machine is a deadly weapon now.
- Really?
- 这个机器现在成了一个致命武器了  - 真的？
The modifications were quite unnecessary.
It worked perfectly well as it was.
这些变动完全不必要, 它之前工作得非常好
For your purposes, perhaps, Professor.
也许, 那只是对你而言, 教授
I have a somewhat different use for it.
我拿它有稍微不一样的用途
All right, all right.
好吧, 好吧
Do with it what you will. The machine's yours now.
你爱怎样就怎样吧, 这台机器现在是你的了
Now, will you let me get out of this place?
现在, 你能允许我离开这个地方了吗？
And let Isobel go free, as you promised?
还有, 你承诺过的, 放 Isobel 走？
- But, my dear fellow, she is free.
- Free?
- 但是, 我亲爱的伙计, 已经放她走了  - 已经走了？
Where? Where is she?
哪儿？她在哪儿？
Probably sitting quite comfortably at home.
很可能正在家里舒服地坐着呢
Now, then...how does one operate this?
现在, 说说...怎么操作这个？
- Careful, Mr Vaughn. Don't point it at anyone.
- No?
- 小心, Vaughn 先生, 不要对着任何人？  - 不要？
Dangerous, is it? Fear, Watkins.
很危险, 是吗？害怕, Watkins
- Do you know what fear is?
- (STAMMERING) No, don't!
- 你知道害怕是什么吗？  - 不, 不要！
(MACHINE PULSATING)
Mr Vaughn, you'll kill him! Stop!
Vaughn 先生, 你会杀死他的！停下！
Perhaps we should try
the effects of the machine on you, Gregory!
也许我们应该在你身上试试这台机器的效果, Gregory!
- At full power!  - No, no. Mr Vaughn.
- 最大功率！  - 不, 不, Vaughn 先生
I was only afraid
that if we still needed the Professor...
我只是担心我们可能还需要教授...
I'm aware of that.
我很明白这一点
Unfortunately, I suppose that I still need you.
Otherwise, I...
很不幸, 我觉得我还需要你．否则, 我...
Pick him up.
抬走他fixme
Professor, you'll be taken back
to the factory compound.
教授, 你会被带回到工业园去
I want these machines
on the production lines immediately.
我要这些机器上生产线, 立刻
- Do you understand?  - Vaughn,
- 明白了吗？  - Vaughn
obviously I can't choose but work for you.
显然我没得选择, 只能为你工作
If I refuse, you'll torture me, you'll kill me.
如果我拒绝, 你会折磨我, 你会杀死我
I know I can't stand up to torture,
我知道我无法忍受折磨
and I don't want to die.
You're an evil man, Vaughn.
而且我不想死．你是一个邪恶的人, Vaughn
You're sadistic. You're a megalomaniac.
你残忍而且自大
You're insane.
你是个疯子
I pity you, but if I get half a chance,
我可怜你, 但如果我找到一点点机会
I'll kill you!
我会杀了你！
Kill me? Would you?
杀了我？ 你会吗？
Give me your gun, Packer.
把你的枪给我, Packer
Take it!
拿着！
There you are. Take it.
给你了, 拿着
Now you're free to shoot me, Professor.
现在你可以朝我开枪了, 教授
Shoot.
开枪
Shoot!
开枪！
Come on, the gun's loaded,
快啊, 子弹已经上膛了
or haven't you got the courage to pull the trigger?
难道你没有勇气扣动一下扳机吗？
Take him away.
Get work started on the machine immediately.
把他带走．立即把机器方面的工作开展起来
UNIT Control to CO.
UNIT Control to CO. Over.
UNIT 控制中心呼叫指挥官, UNIT 控制中心呼叫指挥官, 完毕
Captain Turner here, Sergeant. Stand by.
我是 Turner 队长, 军士．原地待命
- Isobel, will you get the Brigadier for me?
- Oh, sure.
- Isobel, 你能帮我叫一下准将吗？fixme  - 噢, 没问题
Brigadier's on his way now, Sergeant.
What's the flap? Over.
准将过来了, 军士．fixme
-Report from red sector 1, sir, at 2030 hours...
-Hold on a sec.
- 红区１号在20:30发来报告, 长官, 说... - 等一秒钟
Right, the Brigadier's listening now.
Go ahead, Sergeant.
好, 准将在听了, 继续, 军士
Benton on routine observation reports two guards
and another man leaving with the Professor.
Benton 在监视中发现有两个警卫陪同教授离开了, 还有另外一个人
- He is on their tail now, sir. Over.
- Hold on, Sergeant.
- 教授在后面, 长官．完毕  - 等等, 军士
Look, sir, we could intercept
and release the Professor.
你看, 长官, 我们可以进行拦截, 把教授解救出来
- Well, officially we...
- Oh, do! Please do.
- 哦, 场面上我们...  - 噢fixme
Brigadier, if you could rescue him,
he might be able to help us with our problem.
准将, 如果你救出他, 他可能能帮我们解决手头的问题
All right, your shindig, Jimmy.
好吧, 你操办吧, Jimmy
Sergeant, tell Benton to stay with them.
I'm on my way now.
军士, 告诉 Benton 跟着他们fixme．我马上过来
- I'll contact him en route, over.
-Wilco, over.
- 我会在路上联系他, 完毕  - Wilco, 完毕
There were at least 30 of them,
all UNIT men and all armed, Mr Vaughn.
他们至少有３０个人, 都是 UNIT 的人, 全副武装, Vaughn 先生
We didn't stand a chance.
我们一点机会也没有
Out of nowhere. They just came out of nowhere.
突然冒出来了, 他们突然就冒出来了
- And they just took the Professor?
- What could we do?
- 然后他们就把教授抢走了？  - 我们能做啥？
- There were at least...
- Thirty of them, you say?
- 至少有...  - 他们有３０个, 你说？
It was hopeless. They shot the two guards,
完全没希望, 他们开枪打了两个警卫
- and they'd have shot me if...
- If you hadn't run away.
- 而且他们也会开枪打我, 如果... - 如果你没有逃走
Well, yes.
呃, 是的
You realise, of course,
that without the Professor's assistance
你要知道, 当然了, 没有教授的协助
it will not be possible to get
the Cerebraton machine on the production line.
就不可能让精神干扰器上生产线
No, Mr Vaughn, I can.
不, Vaughn 先生, 我可以
Given a little time, I'm sure I can!
给我一点点时间, 我相信我可以！
But you have no time, Gregory.
但你没有时间了, Gregory
No time at all.
一点时间都没有
Kill him!
杀了他！
(CYBERMEN PULSATING)
I'm sorry. I can't tell you.
我很抱歉, 我不能告诉你
You've no idea what these
micromonolithic circuits are for?
你不知道这些微型单晶片电路是做什么的吗？
- No.  - Oh, my word.
- 不知道  - 噢, 天啊
I couldn't understand why Vaughn wanted
the modifications to the machine.
我没法弄明白为什么 Vaughn 想要对机器做那些改动
Why should he want a weapon like that
if he has the Cybermen to fight for him?
为什么他想要一个那样的武器呢, 都已经有赛博人帮他了？
I have no idea. Unless...
我不知道． 除非...
Professor!
教授！
You say that you've developed this machine
to produce excessively powerful emotional pulses.
你说你研制的这个机器可以制造强烈的情绪冲动
- Yes, that's true. - Well, that's it!
- 是的, 是这样  - 那, 这就对了！
Vaughn's going to use it as a weapon against the Cybermen,/?
Vaughn 打算把它用作对付赛博人的武器
once he has no further use for them.
-- 一旦他用不着它们了之后
- What, the Professor's machine?  - Yes.
- 什么, 教授的机器吗？  - 是的
Emotion is alien to the Cybermen's
nervous system. It'll destroy it.
情感对于赛博人的神经系统是异物, 会杀死它
The micromonolithic circuits.
那些微型单晶片电路
They're emotional circuits!
No wonder they weren't logical.
它们是情感电路！ 怪不得它们在逻辑上不通了
Now, why didn't I think of this before?
Now, let's see.
啊, 为什么我早没有想到？ 来, 我们看看
- Now what's he up to? - I've no idea.
- 现在他在搞什么？  - 我不知道
The micromonolithic circuits are
artificial nervous systems.
这些微型单晶体电路是人工的神经系统
Once activated they will produce
the Cyber-hypnotic force
一旦激活, 他们可以产生网络催眠的力量
that controls human beings.
能够控制人类
But there are hundreds, thousands of these
circuits in IE equipment all over the world.
但有成百上千的 IE 公司设备都有这种电路, 遍布全世界
- Exactly.
- So everyone will come under their control.
- 的确  - 所以所有人都会被他们控制
- Yes.
- Yes, the Cybermen will take over everybody.
- 是的  - 是了, 赛博人会控制每个人
Well, isn't there anything that we can do?
那, 有什么我们可以做的吗？
Yes, there is a way to block the signals,
isn't there, Zoe?
有, 有一种方法可以屏蔽这种讯号, 对不, Zoe?
The depolariser.
消偏振器
Worn at the back of the neck,
it will jam the Cyber-control waves.
只要套在脖子后面, 它就可以阻塞赛博控制波
Yes. Have you any neuristors here, Professor?
是的．你这里有神经元器件吗, 博士？
- Well, a few, I think.
- Zoe, show the Professor what to do.
- 哦, 有一些, 我想  - Zoe, 告诉博士该怎么做
The invasion could come at any moment.
入侵可能随时发生
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(WHIRRING)
- Is all in readiness?
- Of course.
- 都准备好了吗？  - 当然
There is one hour to invasion time.
离入侵时间还有一小时
- Countdown will start from now.
- Excellent.
- 现在开始倒计时  - 太好了
We are moving into position now.
我们现在各就各位
Ready to transmit the Cyber-signal.
准备开始传送赛博讯号
(SIGNAL HUMMING)